<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EDA News</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- nav drawer items -->
    <string name="home_category">Home</string>
    <string name="about_category">About</string>
    <string name="faves_category">Faves</string>
    <string name="saved_category">Read Later</string>
    <string name="school_name">Engineering and Digital Arts</string>
    <string name="developer_name">Fitzroy Edinborough</string>
    <string name="about_developer">About Fitzroy Edinborough</string>
    <string name="about_app">EDA News Reader</string>

    <string name="app_about">
        EDA News Reader is the result of an assignment
        in EL881 Android Application Design at University
        of Kent. It was developed by Fitzroy Edinborough,
        a student of EDA\'s Mobile App Design course,
        to demonstrate his proficiency at designing and
        developing apps for the Android platform.
    </string>
    <string name="developer_about">
        Fitzroy Edinborough is a West Indian student
        from the sunny twin-island paradise of
        St Kitts-Nevis. He is the founder of Muscovado,
        a 2015 Commonwealth Scholar, and an avid footballer.
        \n\nGet in contact with him at:
        \n\nfitzroy.edinborough@gmail.com
    </string>
    <string name="school_about">
        The School of Engineering and Digital Arts has an
        excellent reputation for both its teaching and
        research. Based in the Jennison Building on the
        Canterbury Campus, the School has 30 academic staff
        members, with both academic and industrial experience,
        as well as a number of specialist visiting lecturers.
        \n\nYou can find the school at:
        \n\nJennison Building
        \nUniversity of Kent
        \nCanterbury, CT2 7NT
        \nKent, United Kingdom
        \neda@kent.ac.uk
    </string>

    <!--  -->
    <string name="app_title">EDA News Reader</string>

    <!-- faves -->
    <string name="faves_added">Added to Faves</string>
    <string name="faves_removed">Removed from Faves</string>
    <string name="no_faves">Papaya\'s my favourite fruit. Tap the heart to show me your favourite articles.</string>

    <!-- saved -->
    <string name="no_saved">You haven\'t saved any articles, so I saved you this papaya instead.</string>

    <!-- Dummy Strings -->
    <string name="dummy_date">14/12/1988</string>
    <string name="dummy_title">Material is the metaphor Material is the metaphor
        Material is the metaphor Material is the metaphor Material is the metaphor</string>
    <string name="dummy_short_info">
        A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion.
        The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet
        technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.
    </string>
    <string name="dummy_contents">
        A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion.
        The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet
        technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n
        Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The
        use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the
        flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical
        world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n
        The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move,
        interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows
        seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n

        Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n

        The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color,
        and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the
        eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge
        imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic
        interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n
        An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides
        waypoints for the user.\n\n

        Motion provides meaning.\n\n

        Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are
        inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n
        All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without
        breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n
        Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity.
        Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efficient yet coherent.\n\n
    </string>

    <!-- Search strings -->
    <string name="hint_search">Search Titles...</string>
    <string name="no_search">Sorry! \nFound nothing but this juicy papaya.</string>

    <!-- Network messages -->
    <string name="no_network">No network is available.</string>
    <string name="no_network_retry">No network is available. \n Tap to retry.</string>
    <string name="loading_contents">Grabbing details. Gimme a second...</string>

    <!-- Activity Titles -->
    <string name="title_activity_article_details">News Article</string>
    <string name="title_activity_article_search">Search Results</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faves">Fave Articles</string>
    <string name="title_activity_saved">Saved Articles</string>
    <string name="title_none"></string>
</resources>
